Leser, Paul; Papers ger058
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications by other authors, 14; 12.3 cubic ft. 681 file folders
  - Bentzien, Ulrich. "Second International Working Conference for Research on Ploughing Implements", Undated; mimeo, typescript (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 43)
  - Beranová, Magdalena. Untitled typescript, photocopy, Undated (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 44)
  - Berch, Andrea (Anders); reprint, Undated (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 45)
  - Berg, Gösta. "Die schwedische und chinesische Getreidemaschine", Undated; mimeo, typescript, reprints (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 46)
  - "Bericht über die Einsatz bei Tetaigne", author unknown, 1940 May 22; Typescript. (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 47)
  - Berman, Muriel M. "A Conversation with Dr. Muriel M. Berman, Undated; Typescript. (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 48)
  - Bernatzik, Max Hugo Adolf; reprints, Undated (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 49)
  - Berner, Ulrich; reprints, Undated (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 50)
  - Bertholet, Alfred; reprint, Undated (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 51)
  - Bharati, Agehananda; reprints, Undated (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 52)
  - Biasutti, Renato; reprint, Undated (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 53)
  - Bierhenke, Wilhelm; reprints, Undated (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 54)
  - Bijlefeld, Willem A. "Report of and Reflections on a Visit to Pakistan and India January-February 1977", Undated; Typescript. (Box 72 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 55)
  - Black, Isabella; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 1)
  - Black, Lydia T. "Art as a Datum of People's History", Undated; Typescript. (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 2)
  - Blizzard, Samuel W.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 3)
  - Blüher, Hans; covers, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 4)
  - Blümlein, Carl; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 5)
  - Boas, Franz; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 6)
  - Bogucki, Peter I. "Carrying Capacity Models and the Early Neolithic of Central Europe", Undated; Typescript. (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 7)
  - Bonino, José Míguez. "Theological Education for a Church in Transition", Undated; Typescript. (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 8)
  - Bordaz, Jacques; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 9)
  - Bornemann, E.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 10)
  - Bornemann, Fritz; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 11)
  - Bosch-Gimpera, Pedro; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 12)
  - Bose, Walter B. L.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 13)
  - Bradley, William. "Religion and Public Affairs", Undated; typescript, reprint (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 14)
  - Braidwood, Robert J.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 15)
  - Brandewie, Ernest. "Wilhelm Schmidt and the Roots of the Methodology of Culture-History", Undated; typescript, reprint (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 16)
  - Bratani?, Branimir; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 17)
  - Bratani?, Branimir; manuscripts, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 18)
  - Brentjes, Burchard. "Über das Problem des Verwendungszwecke der Schuhleisten-keile des Neolithikums", Undated; Typescript. (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 19)
  - Brentjes, Burchard; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 20)
  - Bringéus, Nils-Arvid; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 21)
  - Brönner, Wolfgang; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 22)
  - Brokensha, David W.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 23)
  - Bromley, David; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 24)
  - Brown, Harrison. "How Big Need a Big Bomb Be?", Undated; Typescript. (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 25)
  - Buckman, Chester A. "Musca Domestica (An Unfinished Soliloquy)", Undated; Typescript. (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 26)
  - Bühler, Alfred; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 27)
  - Buettner-Janusch, John; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 28)
  - Bullen, A. K.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 29)
  - Burckhardt-Seebass, Christine; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 30)
  - Burgmann, Arnold; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 31)
  - Byhan, Arthur; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 32)
  - Campbell, ?ke; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 33)
  - Cardoso, Carlos Lopes; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 34)
  - Carneiro, Robert L.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 35)
  - Cederström, Rudolf; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 36)
  - Chakerian, Charles G.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 37)
  - Chamberlain, John; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 38)
  - Chernoff, John Miller; abstract, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 39)
  - Civrieux, Marc de; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 40)
  - Clark, Walter Houston. "The Place of Drugs in the Religion of the Counter Culture", Undated; typescript, reprints (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 41)
  - Cline, Howard F.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 42)
  - Cloete, Stuart; clippings, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 43)
  - Closs, Alois; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 44)
  - Coelho, Maria Angelina Teixeira; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 45)
  - Comas, Juan; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 46)
  - Comhaire-Sylvan, S.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 47)
  - Conklin, Harold C.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 48)
  - Coulborn, Rushton. "Uniformities in History", Undated; typescript, reprints (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 49)
  - Count, Earl W.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 50)
  - Cox, Harvey L.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 51)
  - Cragg, Kenneth. "Near East Christian Council Study Program in Islam", Undated; mimeo, typescript (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 52)
  - Cressy, Earl Herbert. "City Churches in East Asia", Undated; Typescript. (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 53)
  - Dahlberg, Albert A.; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 54)
  - Dalquen, J. M.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 55)
  - Darnell, Regna; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 56)
  - Daudi, Philippe; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 57)
  - de Josselin de Jong, P. E.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 58)
  - Delamarre, Mariel J.-Brunhes. "L'outillage agricole premachniste en Bretagne", Undated; mimeo, typescript (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 59)
  - "Dem Andenken an Gregor Mendel"; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 60)
  - Desroche, Henri; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 61)
  - Dettmer, Bob. "The Blue Journal", Undated; mimeo, typescript (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 62)
  - DeWalt, Billie R.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 63)
  - Diamond, Stanley; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 64)
  - Dias, Jorge; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 65)
  - Dias, Margot; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 66)
  - Diggs, Irene; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 67)
  - Dittmer, Kunz; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 68)
  - Dodd/Wainwright. "The Leading Question", Undated; Typescript. (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 69)
  - Dohna, Graf zu; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 70)
  - Dosedla, Heinz-Christian; reprints, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 71)
  - Douglas, Elmer H.; reprint, Undated (Box 73 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 72)
  - Duffey, Joseph. "Law and Society". Typescript; "The Corporation and the Individual". Typescript, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 1)
  - Dunger, George A. "An African Marriage Survey", Undated; mimeo, typescript (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 2)
  - Dunn, Stephen P. "Notes on Aims, Methods, and Style in Current Soviet Ethnography", Undated; Typescript. (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 3)
  - Dupierreux, Richard; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 4)
  - du Toit, Brian M. "The Development and Profession of Anthropology in the Netherlands", Undated; Typescript. (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 5)
  - Ebeling, Walter; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 6)
  - Eberhard, Wolfram; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 7)
  - Eckert, Georg; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 8)
  - Edel, Abraham; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 9)
  - Edel, May; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 10)
  - Egenter, Nold; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 11)
  - Ehrich, Robert W. "On the Persistences and Recurrences of Culture Areas and Culture Boundaries During the Course of European Prehistory, Protohistory, and History". Mimeo. typescript; "Ceramics and Man: A Cultural Perspective". Mimeo. typescript, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 12)
  - Ehrich, Robert W.; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 13)
  - Elbert, Joh.; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 14)
  - Emsheimer, Ernst; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 15)
  - Epstein, Klaus; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 16)
  - Eriksson, Manne; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 17)
  - Erixson, Sigurd; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 18-19)
  - Erixson, Sigurd; manuscripts, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 20)
  - Estel, Leo; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 21)
  - Estermann, Carlos; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 22)
  - Fahnbulleh, Fatima M.; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 23)
  - Farmer, Malcolm F.; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 24)
  - Feilberg, Carl Gunnar; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 25)
  - Feldkeller, Paul; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 26)
  - Fennelly, Catherine. "The Industrial Revolution and the New England Village, 1790-1840", Undated; Typescript. (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 27)
  - Fenton, Alexander; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 28)
  - Fenton, William N.; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 29)
  - Finestone, Harold; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 30)
  - Finscher, Helmut; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 31)
  - Fischer, J. L. "Ethnic Relations on Ponape, 1800 to Present", Undated; Typescript. (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 32)
  - Fishman, Leo; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 33)
  - Fishwick, Marshall; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 34)
  - Flor, Fritz; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 35)
  - Foerster, Erich; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 36)
  - Forni, Gaetano; reprints; manuscripts, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 37)
  - Fouss, E.-P.; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 38)
  - Frantz, Ch. "The 20th Century Development of U.S. Anthropology: Universities, Government, and the Private Sector", Undated; Typescript. (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 39)
  - Fraser, Douglas; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 40)
  - Freilich, Morris. "The Comparative Method: Name it a rose and twill sweetly smell", Undated; Typescript. (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 41)
  - Fried, Morton H.; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 42)
  - Friederici, G.; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 43)
  - Friedl, Ernestine; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 44)
  - Friedlaender, Benedict; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 45)
  - Friis, Herman R. "The Cartographic Record: A Challenging Source for the Study of the History of the United States", Undated; Typescript. (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 46)
  - Frimannslund, Rigmor; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 47)
  - Frobenius, Leo; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 48)
  - Gabel, C.; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 49)
  - Ganslmayr, Herbert; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 50)
  - Garn, Stanley M.; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 51)
  - Geertz, Clifford; reprint, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 52)
  - Gesell, Silvio; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 53)
  - Gleason, H. A. Jr.; reprints, Undated (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 54)
  - Gleason, H. A. Jr. "Introduction to Descriptive Linguistics", Undated; Typescript. (Box 74 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 55-56)
  - Gleason, H. A. Jr. "The Architecture of Language and the Strategy of Description", Undated; Typescript. (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 1)
  - Goetz, Hans Herbert; clippings, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 2)
  - Goetz, Hermann; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 3)
  - Goff, Charles W.; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 4)
  - Goldschmidt, Walter; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 5)
  - Golightly, Cornelius L.; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 6)
  - Good, Paul; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 7)
  - Granlund, John; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 8)
  - Grau, Rudolf; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 9)
  - Graul, Ilse; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 10)
  - Greenberg, Leon A.; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 11)
  - Gretzer, W.; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 12)
  - Gropengießer, Hermann; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 13)
  - Grosse, E.; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 14)
  - Grottanelli, Vinigi L.; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 15)
  - Grounds, Vernon. "The Case Against Cooperation with the National Council and the World Council of Churches", Undated; Typescript. (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 16)
  - Gunda, Béla; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 17)
  - Gunn, Harold D.; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 18)
  - Gusinde, Martin; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 19)
  - Haberland, Eike; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 20)
  - Haddad, Anis Charles; bibliography, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 21)
  - Hadidjian, Dikran. "Prinderella and the Cince" and "The Mion and the Louse". Typescripts, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 22)
  - Haekel, Josef; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 23)
  - Hagen, B.; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 24)
  - Hallowell, A. Irving; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 25)
  - Halpern, Joel. "East European Peasantries -- Interwar Perspectives from Economics, Ethnology and Social Anthropology", Undated; Typescript. (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 26)
  - Handsman, Russell G. "Machines and Gardens: Structures in and Symbols of America's Past", Undated; Typescript. (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 27)
  - Hartmann, Horst; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 28)
  - Haudricourt, André G.; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 29)
  - Heath, Dwight B. "Land Tenure and Social Organization: An Ethnohistorical Study from the Bolivian Orients", Undated; mimeo, typescript (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 30)
  - Hecker, Howard M. "Domestication Reconsidered: Its Implications for Faunal Analysis", Undated; mimeo, typescript (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 31)
  - Hedden, Mark; reprints, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 32)
  - Hedden, Mark. "Evidence for Eurasian Influences on the Prehistoric Art of the Columbia River, Washington and Other Areas of the Western Hemisphere", Undated; Typescript. (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 33)
  - Hedin, Svend; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 34)
  - Heimpel, Hermann; reprint, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 35)
  - Heine-Geldern, Robert; reprints, 1930s-1940s (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 36)
  - Heine-Geldern, Robert; reprints, 1950s (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 37)
  - Heine-Geldern, Robert; reprints, 1960s (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 38)
  - Heine-Geldern, Robert. "One Hundred Years of Ethnological Theory in the German-Speaking Countries: Some Milestones", (December 1964); numerous copies (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 39)
  - Heine-Geldern, Robert, Undated; manuscripts (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 40)
  - Helwig, Werner; reprints, clippings, Undated (Box 75 (14-Series 14 - Manuscripts, reprints and publications), Folder 41)